https://yardcare.toro.com/privacy-notice/

Privacy Notice
TORO
PRIVACY POLICY
Toro’s Commitment to Your Privacy
The Toro Company respects your privacy.  Toro provides this Privacy Policy so you know about Toro’s online information practices and understand how Toro treats the information we receive about you from your use of this web site (the “Site”).  This Policy applies, in general, to all Internet sites operated by or on behalf of Toro and its business units worldwide. By using, browsing and/or accessing this Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Use of this Site is strictly voluntary.  If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy and Web Site Terms and Conditions of Use, you must immediately log off the Site and may not use the Site.
The Information Toro Collects
In general, you can browse this Site without telling Toro who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.  Toro is, however, able to determine your IP address.  Toro uses your IP address to, among other things, (1) help diagnose problems with Toro’s server, administer the Site, measure the use of the Site, improve the content of the Site; (2) to identify visitors’ domain names, the type of web browsers used, the pages viewed, the websites from which a visitor found this Site, the search terms and search engines used to find this Site; and (3) to gather other web analytics information relating to visitors’ use and navigation of the Site.
There are a few places where Toro gives you an opportunity to provide Toro your personal information.  This refers to information that lets Toro know the specifics of who you are, and may include, without limitation, your first and last name; mailing address, email address, telephone and facsimile numbers, credit card number, and other personal identifying information.  When you engage in certain activities on the Site, such as ordering a product or service; entering a contest or sweepstakes; participating in social media activities involving things such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, or Foursquare, whether at this Site or the social media web sites; filling out a survey; sending feedback or product reviews; requesting owners and parts manuals; or registering your product online; Toro may ask you to provide personal information.  If you choose to share any personal information with Toro, you will see that the amount and type of personal information Toro requests depends on how you use the Site.  It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities.  Depending upon the activity, some of the information Toro asks you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is voluntary.  If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
Additionally, the Site employs the use of cookies in certain areas. Cookies are small bits of information stored on your browser.  Cookies enable browsers to “remember” information related to a specific user, and also improve navigational reliability within a given site.  The use of cookies allows Toro to recognize you every time you visit, and to personalize the Site to better suit your needs.  If you are uncomfortable with storing cookies on your browser, you may set your browser specifically to reject cookies.
The Way Toro Uses Information
Toro may use your personal information for particular activities, including, without limitation, processing your order; credit card processing; collections; returns management; manufacturing; storage; shipping; delivery; fulfillment; customer service; marketing and research; providing product, promotional and other information to you; and to contact you regarding administrative notices.  Toro may share this information with Toro’s affiliates, dealers or other business partners in connection with any of the foregoing activities.  Toro’s affiliates, dealers or other business partners may use this information for marketing and solicitation purposes.  Toro must release your credit card information to credit card authorization service providers and the credit card-issuing bank to confirm and settle payment for products or services purchased on this Site and to facilitate returns or refunds.  Except as described above, Toro will not give or sell your personal information to any other company for its use in marketing or solicitation.
Toro may disclose personal information in any of the following circumstances: (1) in response to a subpoena, search warrant, court order, or other legal process or request, or as may otherwise be required by applicable law or regulation; (2) to protect and defend Toro’s rights or property or those of its affiliates, dealers, business partners, or others; or (3) as Toro, in its sole discretion, believes is appropriate under exigent circumstances in response to a perceived threat to the personal safety or property of any person or organization.
In addition, since Toro’s database is a business asset, in the event Toro is reorganized or is sold to or merged with another company, you consent to the sale, assignment, or transfer of your personal information to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Toro’s business assets, or to an affiliate, as applicable.
Processing of your Personal Information.
This Site is currently hosted on servers located within the United States, but the locations of Toro’s servers may change from time-to-time.  Your personal information may be stored on servers located within the United States, or in another country.  In addition, Toro may transfer your personal information to affiliates, dealers, business partners, or others located in the United States or other countries in accordance with, and for the purposes as described in, this Privacy Policy. Different countries have different privacy laws and requirements.
BY SUBMITTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO TORO, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES OR IN ANY OTHER COUNTRY IN THE WORLD.
Retention of your Personal Information
Toro keeps your personal information as long as Toro needs it for the purposes for which it was originally collected (or to which you have subsequently consented), for other legitimate purposes (such as regulatory compliance), or as permitted by applicable law.  Since some of these activities may continue for an extended period of time, Toro may keep your personal information indefinitely.
Toro’s Relationship to other Sites that can be Accessed through this Site
This Site may contain links to other web sites.  Additionally, other web sites may contain links to this Site.  Toro does not review or monitor the web sites linked to this Site and is not responsible for the contents, terms of use, or privacy policies related to any other web sites.  Where this Site contains a link to another web site owned and/or operated by Toro, such web site use may be subject to different and additional terms of use and privacy policies.
Other Information You should Know about your Privacy
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) prohibits certain commercial practices related to gathering, storing, and disclosing personal information about children under the age of 13 who use the Internet.  Toro will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.  Toro cannot prohibit minors from browsing this Site, or using this Site if they supply valid security or identification information (for instance, a username and password issued to another person, such as a parent or friend).  Toro must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervision of children to monitor the Internet activities of children under the age of 13.  Each time you submit personally identifiable information about yourself or your family through the Site, you are representing to Toro that your are 18 years of age or older.
All electronic communication services such as the ones provided by Toro are required to comply with the “mandatory reporting” requirements of 42 U.S.C. § 13032(b), which requires such services to report any apparent child pornography to the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children.  In the event Toro is required to make a report, it will include all information regarding the apparent child pornography it believes may be of importance. Toro will strictly comply with this reporting requirement.
Access and Correction of your Personal Information
Toro strives to maintain the accuracy and integrity of the personal information in its databases and to keep that information up-to-date.  Toro provides ways for you to access your personal information as required by applicable law, so that you can correct inaccuracies or update your personal information.  Toro reserves the right to charge a fee as permitted by applicable law.
If you would like to review or correct your personal information, please contact Toro by email at Legal@toro.com or send a letter to:
The Toro Company
Attn: Legal Department
8111 Lyndale Avenue South
Bloomington, MN 55420-1196.
All communications must be in the English language.
Toro will respond to reasonable requests within the time limits established by applicable law or within a reasonable time if no time limit is established by applicable law.  For your protection, Toro may ask you for additional information to verify your identity.  In most cases, Toro will provide the access you request and correct or delete any inaccurate personal information you discover.  Toro reserves the right, however, to limit or deny your request to the extent permitted by applicable law if: (1) the disclosure may harm the personal safety or property of any person or organization; (2) the disclosure may lead to a violation of applicable laws or regulations; or (3) where you have failed to provide sufficient evidence to verify your identity.  Toro encourages you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.
Toro’s Commitment to Security of Your Personal Information
Toro takes what it believes to be reasonable precautions and has implemented managerial and technical procedures to try to protect the security of data and information, including personal information.  Toro strives to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness, and current status of personal information and to protect the privacy and security of such.  Toro cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration or destruction of data or personal information.  While Toro strives to protect your personal information, Toro cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to or from this Site, and you provide such information at your own risk.  You acknowledge that: (1) there are security and privacy limitations in computer systems and on the Internet which are beyond Toro’s control; (2) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and Toro through the Site, including personal information, cannot be guaranteed; and (3) any such information and data, including personal information, may be viewed or tampered with by a third party while such information or data is being used, transmitted, processed, or stored.
Changes to Privacy Policy
Toro reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time without notice to you. You expressly waive any right to receive notice of any changes to this Privacy Policy.  Toro encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly in your use of the Site to ensure you are aware of current practices.  Any use of the Site following the date on which Toro implements changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of all such changes.
Categories
blog
choosing the right grass
connect
controlling weeds
create
equipment safety
features
